bevywise.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy Policy - IoT Simulator for MQTT Protocol - Bevywise Networks

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ is being used online. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Information in accordance with our website 

## What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering, downloading products or contacting us on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

## When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you fill out a form, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site or when you provide us with feedback on our products or services.

## How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested
  * To allow us to serve you better, in responding to your customer service requests
  * To write to you to get your feedback on the product
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
  * To follow up after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries).

## How do we protect your information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning.

## How do we protect your information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning.

## Do we use ‘cookies’?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled, that make your site experience less efficient and may not function properly.

However, you will still be able to place orders. 

## Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

## Third-party links

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
